
Viewing and saving images from your Downloaded Zip File or your CD
1.  Access the Files
	CD:  	Insert the CD (CD may load content automatically based on your computer settings)
		WINDOWS: From the Start Menu click on ‘Computer’
		MAC: Open ‘Finder’
		Double click on the disk drive labeled PhotoCD (D:)
	Zip File: Save and Extract all files into a folder on your hard drive
		Open the folder containing the new files
2.  To view image files:
		Open ‘images\my_images’ folder
3.  To save image files, simply drag and drop onto desktop or into any folder on your hard drive.
4.  To launch interactive menu:
		WINDOWS: Double click ‘main.exe’   
		MAC: Select the application labeled ‘main’
5.  To view full screen slideshow:
		Click ‘My Images’
		Click ‘Slideshow’ button (bottom center) 
6.  Collage Backgrounds:  
	English: Open ‘PremiumContent’ folder for instructions in the PDF file: ‘MarathonFoto Premium Content - EN.pdf’
	French:	 Open ‘PremiumContent’ folder for instructions in the PDF file: ‘MarathonFoto Premium Content - FR.pdf’



Pour afficher et enregistrer des images depuis votre fichier Zip téléchargé ou votre CD
1.  Pour accéder aux fichiers
	CD : Insérez le CD (en fonction de la configuration de votre ordinateur, le contenu du CD pourra s'afficher automatiquement).
		WINDOWS : Dans le menu 'Démarrer', cliquez sur 'Ordinateur'.
		MAC : Ouvrez le 'Finder'.
		Cliquez deux fois sur le lecteur de disque contenant votre CD de photos (D:, par exemple)
	Fichier Zip : Enregistrez votre archive Zip, puis extrayez tous les fichiers qu'elle contient dans un dossier sur votre disque dur.
		Ouvrez le dossier contenant les fichiers.
2.  Pour afficher vos images :
		Ouvrez le dossier 'images\my_images'.
3.  Pour enregistrer des fichiers d'images, glissez-déposez ces fichiers sur votre bureau ou dans tout autre dossier de votre disque dur.
4.  Pour lancer le menu interactif :
		WINDOWS : Cliquez deux fois sur le fichier 'main.exe'.
		MAC : Sélectionnez l'application 'main'.
5.  Pour afficher le diaporama en plein écran :
		Cliquez sur 'My Images'.
		Cliquez sur le bouton 'Diaporama' (dans la partie inférieure de la fenêtre, au centre). 
6.  Maquettes de photomontages :
	Anglais : Dans le dossier 'PremiumContent', ouvrez le fichier 'MarathonFoto Premium Content - EN.pdf' pour obtenir des instructions d'utilisation.
	Français : Dans le dossier 'PremiumContent', ouvrez le fichier 'MarathonFoto Premium Content - FR.pdf' pour obtenir des instructions d'utilisation.




Kuvien tarkastelu ja tallennus ladatusta Zip-tiedostosta tai CD-levyltä
1.  Tiedostojen käyttö
	CD:  	Aseta CD-levy tietokoneeseen (tietokoneen asetusten mukaan CD:n sisältö saatetaan ladata automaattisesti).
		WINDOWS: Napsauta Käynnistä-valikosta Tietokone-painiketta.
		MAC: Avaa Finder.
		Kaksoisosoita levyasemaa nimeltä PhotoCD (D:).
	Zip-tiedosto: Tallenna ja pura kaikki tiedostot kiintolevyllä olevaan kansioon.
		Avaa uudet tiedostot sisältävä kansio.
2.  Kuvatiedostojen tarkastelu:
		Avaa kansio nimeltä images\my_images.
3.  Kuvatiedostot voi tallentaa vetämällä ja pudottamalla ne työpöydälle tai johonkin kiintolevyllä olevaan kansioon.
4.  Vuorovaikutteisen valikon käynnistäminen:
		WINDOWS: Kaksoisnapsauta main.exe-tiedostoa.   
		MAC: Valitse main-niminen ohjelma.
5.  Koko näytön diaesityksen tarkastelu:
		Napsauta My Images -kohtaa.
		Napsauta Slideshow-painiketta (alhaalla keskellä). 
6.  Kollaasitaustat:  
	Englanti: Avaa PremiumContent-kansio, joka sisältää ohjeet PDF-tiedostossa: MarathonFoto Premium Content – EN.pdf.




Bilder aus Ihrer heruntergeladenen Zip-Datei oder von Ihrer CD anzeigen und speichern
1.  So greifen Sie auf die Dateien zu:
	CD:  	Legen Sie die CD ein (je nach den Einstellungen Ihres Computers wird der CD-Inhalt ggf. automatisch geladen).
		WINDOWS: Klicken Sie im Start-Menü auf die Option „Computer“.        
		MAC: Öffnen Sie den Finder.
		Doppelklicken Sie auf das Laufwerk mit dem Namen „PhotoCD“ (D:).
	Zip-Datei: Extrahieren Sie alle Dateien und speichern Sie sie in einem Ordner auf Ihrer Festplatte.
		Öffnen Sie den Ordner mit den neuen Dateien.
2.  So zeigen Sie die Bilddateien an:
		Öffnen Sie den Ordner „images\my_images“.
3.  Um die Bilddateien zu speichern, ziehen Sie sie einfach per Drag&Drop auf den Desktop oder in einen beliebigen Ordner auf Ihrer Festplatte.
4.  So starten Sie das interaktive Menü:
		WINDOWS: Doppelklicken sie auf die Datei „main.exe“.   
		MAC: Wählen Sie die Anwendung „main“.
5.  So zeigen Sie die Vollbild-Diashow an:
		Klicken Sie auf „My Images“.
		Klicken Sie auf die Schaltfläche für die Diashow (Mitte unten). 
6.  Collagenhintergründe:  
	Englisch: Eine Anleitung hierzu enthält die PDF-Datei “MarathonFoto Premium Content - EN.pdf“ im Ordner „PremiumContent“.




Visualizzazione e salvataggio di immagini dal file zip scaricato o dal CD
1.  Accesso ai file
	CD:  	Inserire il CD (che può caricare il contenuto automaticamente in base alle impostazioni del computer)
		WINDOWS: Nel menu Start fare clic su “Computer”        
		MAC: Aprire Finder
		Fare doppio clic sull’unità disco “PhotoCD (D:)”
	File zip: Salvare lo zip ed estrarre tutti i file in una cartella o nel disco rigido
		Aprire la cartella che contiene i nuovi file
2.  Per vedere i file di immagine:
		Aprire la cartellaimages\my_images
3.  Per salvare i file di immagine, è sufficiente trascinarli sul desktop o in qualsiasi cartella del disco rigido.
4.  Per avviare il menu interattivo:
		WINDOWS: Fare doppio clic su main.exe   
		MAC: Selezionare l’applicazione “main”
5.  Per vedere la presentazione a tutto schermo:
		Fare clic su “My Images”
		Fare clic sul pulsante “Slideshow” (al centro nella parte inferiore) 
6.  Sfondi di collage:  
	Inglese: Le istruzioni sono disponibili nella cartella “PremiumContent”, file PDF: “MarathonFoto Premium Content - EN.pdf”




Como visualizar e salvar imagens a partir do arquivo zip baixado ou do CD
1.  Acesse os arquivos
	CD:  	Insira o CD (o conteúdo pode ser carregado automaticamente, dependendo das configurações do computador)
		WINDOWS: No menu Iniciar, clique em Computador        
		MAC: Abra o Finder
		Clique duas vezes na unidade de disco denominada PhotoCD (D:)
	Arquivo zip: Salve e extraia todos os arquivos em uma pasta no seu disco rígido
		Abra a pasta contendo os novos arquivos
2.  Para ver os arquivos de imagem:
		Abra a pasta images\my_images
3.  Para salvar os arquivos de imagem, basta arrastá-los e soltá-los na área de trabalho ou dentro de uma pasta no seu disco rígido.
4.  Para abrir o menu interativo:
		WINDOWS: Clique duas vezes em main.exe   
		MAC: Selecione o aplicativo denominado Main
5.  Para ver uma apresentação de slides em tela inteira:
		Clique em Minhas Imagens
		Clique no botão de Apresentação de Slides (embaixo, no centro) 
6.  Fundos para colagem:  
	Inglês: Abra a pasta PremiumContent para obter instruções no arquivo PDF: MarathonFoto Premium Content - EN.pdf




Ver y guardar las imágenes de un archivo comprimido descargado o un CD
1.  Acceder a los archivos
	CD:  	Introduzca el CD (el CD puede cargar el contenido de forma automática en función de la configuración del equipo)
		WINDOWS: En el menú Inicio, haga clic en Mi PC        
		MAC: Abra el Finder
		Haga doble clic en la unidad de disco llamada PhotoCD (D:)
	Archivo comprimido: Extraiga y guarde los archivos en una carpeta de la unidad de disco duro
		Abra la carpeta que contiene los archivos nuevos
2.  Para ver los archivos de imagen:
		Abra la carpeta images\my_images
3.  Para guardar los archivos de imagen, arrastre y suéltelos en el escritorio o en cualquier carpeta de la unidad de disco duro.
4.  Para iniciar el menú interactivo:
		WINDOWS: Haga doble clic en main.exe   
		MAC: Seleccione la aplicación llamada main
5.  Para ver la presentación de diapositivas a pantalla completa:
		Haga clic en Mis imágenes
		Haga clic en el botón Presentación de diapositivas (botón central) 
6.  Fondos collage:  
	Inglés: Vaya a la carpeta PremiumContent y abra el documento MarathonFoto Premium Content - EN.pdf para consultar las instrucciones.




Visa och spara bilder från den hämtade zip-filen eller CD-skivan
1.  Få åtkomst till filerna
	CD:  	Stoppa in CD-skivan (beroende på datorns inställningar kan det hända att innehållet på skivan öppnas automatiskt)
		WINDOWS: Klicka på Dator i Start-menyn        
		MAC: Öppna Finder
		Dubbelklicka på diskenheten med namnet PhotoCD (D:)
	Zip-fil: Spara och extrahera alla filer till en mapp på hårddisken
		Öppna mappen med de nya filerna
2.  Visa bildfiler:
		Öppna mappen images\my_images
3.  Om du vill spara bildfiler drar och släpper du dem på skrivbordet eller i en mapp på hårddisken.
4.  Starta den interaktiva menyn:
		WINDOWS: Dubbelklicka på main.exe   
		MAC: Välj programmet med namnet main
5.  Visa bildspel på hela skärmen:
		Klicka på My Images
		Klicka på bildspelsknappen (längst ned i mitten) 
6.  Bakgrunder till collage:  
	Engelska: Öppna mappen PremiumContent för anvisningar i PDF-filen: MarathonFoto Premium Content - EN.pdf





Last Updated: 20140808